Preliminary Guide to the Columbian Women records, 1894-2009 RG0027
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Columbian Women records
1894-2009
1916-2006
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Stoltz, Ramona
RG0027
16 Linear Feet
Collection includes scrapbooks, reports, correspondence, member lists, constitution and by-laws, photographs, and meeting minutes.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from Columbian Women.
Historical or Biographical Note
In 1894, a fire at Ford's Theater took the life of the father of Mary Chapin, one of the original thirteen women to attend Columbian University (it became The George Washington University in 1904). So that she could continue her education, the women students, under the guidance of Professor Charles Munroe, formed a group called "Columbian Women," and raised money for Mary to finish her studies. Membership was open to women students, alumnae, and wives of faculty, trustees, and officers of the University.
The major aims of the organization are the advancement of women at the University and the promotion of the interests of their alma mater. The major portion of Columbian Women's activities is the support of its Scholarship Fund for women students. The first fund was established in 1897 and since then hundreds of young women have been helped through this Fund. Three first ladies of the United States have been interested in the scholarship program - Mrs. Calvin Coolidge, Mrs. Herbert Hoover, and Mrs. Harry Truman. Mrs. Truman entertained Columbian Women members at a White House tea while her husband was in office. Over the years, the organization has also given generous gifts to the University itself, including the hospital, Women's Athletics, and the University Library.
Many distinguished women have been members, among them novelists Dorothy Betts Marvin (wife of former GW President Cloyd Heck Marvin), Mary Roberts Rinehart and Margaret Truman, Judge Sarah T. Hughes, who administered the oath of office to President Lyndon Johnson after President John F. Kennedy's death, aviatrix Jackie Cochran, and the Director of the U.S. Mint, Eva Adams.
N.B. This history note was written in 2005
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include scrapbooks, reports, correspondence, financial records, constitution and by-laws, photographs, and meeting minutes. They range in date from 1894 to 2009, and were transferred to the University Archives by the historians of the Columbian Women.
There is historical materials related to Columbian Women in MS2278. These materials were gathered by member Dr. Ruth Osborn.
Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized in eight series: Columbian Women, records, 1916-1980; Columbian Women, records, 1988-2003; Scrapbooks prepared by Columbian Women historians; History of Columbian Women, scholarships and applications, minutes, correspondence, and treasurer's reports; Treasurer's records, correspondence, and Scholarship Committee; Directories, events, and history; Videotapes; and Ramona Stoltz papers.
Photographs; Scrapbooks; By-laws; Washington (D.C.); Meetings; Scholarships; Events; Columbian Women, George Washington University, Washington (D.C.); Stoltz, Ramona; George Washington University
- Columbian Women, records, 1916-1980; Series 1; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains the records of the Columbian Women from 1916 to 1980, including annual reports, minutes, correspondence, scholarship funds and recipients, constitution and by-laws, photographs, and material on the 75th and 90th anniversaries.
  - Annual Reports of Officers, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Includes Treasurers' Reports
  - Minutes of Annual and Program Meetings, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Meetings and Minutes, 1965 -1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Audits, Budgets, Finance, 1951-1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Treasurers' Reports and Scholarship Funds Reports, 1958-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Scholarship Reports and Miscellaneous, 1967-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship Holders, 1916-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Memorial Committee, 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Jessie Fant Evans Scholarship Fund, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Marcia B. Kraft Scholarship Fund, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Columbian Women Programs--Announcements, etc., 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Diamond Jubilee, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Related correspondence also included.
  - Embassy Tour Benefit, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Includes Handbook of Duties and the Procedures of Officers and Committee Chairmen, March 1970
  - Columbian Woman, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Columbian Woman, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Columbian Woman, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Columbian Woman, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Columbian Woman, 75th Anniversary, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Columbian Woman, 90th Anniversary, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Various Contents, 1925-1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Program for 17th Annual Dinner of the Columbian Women, 1925; The GWU Highschool Press Conference Program, 1942; Student Financial Aid brochure, 1971-1972
  - Scrapbook, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Photos, letters, and clippings from Embassy Tour, presented to Sue Bernett Panzer
- Columbian Women, records, 1988-2003; Series 2; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains the records of the Columbian Women from 1988 to 2003, including annual reports, by-laws, membership directories, scholarship committee, budgets, scrapbook of clippings and photographs. Donated by Janet Bergman.
  - Columbian Women - Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Columbian Women - Annual Reports, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Columbian Women - Auditors' Report, 07/1998-08/2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Columbian Women - Bylaws Revision, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Columbian Women - Directory Executive Committee, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Columbian Women - Directory, 12/01/1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Columbian Women - Directory, 01/01/1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Columbian Women - Directory, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Columbian Women - Dr. Estelle S. Phillips Gifts and Bequest, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Columbian Women - Edwin C. Fishel Memorial, 06/1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Columbian Women - Elizabeth R. Heckman, Member and Benefactor, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Columbian Women - Executive Committee/Board, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Columbian Women - Federal Tax Return, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Columbian Women - Financial Reports, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Columbian Women - Frances Ware Moore Eulogy, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Columbian Women - GW Alumni Service Award Nominations, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Columbian Women - Membership directory and by-laws with diskette, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Columbian Women - Membership Directory, 11/2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Columbian Women - Membership Meeting Minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Columbian Women - Membership Directory, 02/2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    2 copies
  - Columbian Women - Memorandum for the Executive Committee and request for approval of scholarship awards, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Columbian Women - Miscellaneous Correspondence of President, 09/1999 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Columbian Women - Nomination of Recent Alumni Trustee Ramona Stoltz, 11/28/2000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Columbian Women - Program Announcements, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Columbian Women - Publicity, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Columbian Women - Scholarship Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Columbian Women - Scholarship Committee, 06/1999-11/2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Columbian Women - Scholarship Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Columbian Women - Scholarship Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Columbian Women - Scholarship Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Columbian Women - Scholarship Documents, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Columbian Women - Scholarship Recipients and Letters of Appreciation, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Columbian Women - Vitaes of Officers, 1993-2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Columbian Women - Yearly Budgets, 1998-2003 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Columbian Women - Minutes and bylaws, 1988-1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Loose - binder
  - Columbian Women - Meeting minutes, 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Columbian Women - Scrapbook, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Scrapbooks prepared by Columbian Women historians (includes executive committee minutes 1890-1945), 1894-1985; Series 3; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 2, Box 4, Box 1A, Box 5)
  This series contains scrapbooks prepared by Columbian Women historians from 1894 to 1985.
  - History/Scrapbook (loose), 1990 (Box 1B, Folder 5)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1983-1985 (Box 1B, Folder 3-4)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1981-1983 (Box 1B, Folder 2)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1979-1981 (Box 1B, Folder 1)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1977-1979 (Box 1A)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1975-1976 (Box 1A)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Photobook, 1940 ca.-1960 ca. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Few photos, mostly from 1960s
  - Scrapbook, 1960 ca. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, 1960 ca. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook of news clippings, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Poor condition
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1933-1936 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1931-1932 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1906-1908 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - History/Scrapbooks, 1894-1924 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Momento Book, 1910-1933 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1937-1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1933-1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1916-1927 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1910-1916 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1905-1907 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1890-1910 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Videotape - Columbian Women 90th anniversary play, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    3/4 inch videotape
- History of Columbian Women, scholarships and applications, minutes, correspondence, and treasurer's reports, 1947-1986; Series 4; 3 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series includes the history of Columbian Women, scholarships and applications, minutes, correspondence, and treasurer's reports. They date from 1947 to 1986.
  - History of Columbian Women, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Luncheon at the Cosmos Club, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Columbian Women: Scholarships: Marie-Louise Turner Fund, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Treasury Nates and Bills, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship Applications, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Andolfatto, Fiola, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Albert, Marjorie, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Grades, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Kaplan, Louis L., undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Fineblum, Carol M., undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Trucks, Elizabeth McWane, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Wilson, Joyce, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Boteler, Marcia, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sheppy, Phyllis, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Watkins, Peggy Jane, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Langerman, Elaine M., undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Evenson, Norma D., undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Weisskopf, Vera Jordan, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Griffith, Mary C., undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Weaver, Patricia, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Soborsky, Emily, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Zigmond, Faye, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Diament, Lila, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Oreamuno, Diana, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Linde, Ann, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Haas, Diana Marie, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Brown, Meyer and Betty, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Chaconas, Frances, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - MacEwen, Ellen Mae, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Pinch, Anita Porro, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Lebowitz, Marilyn Sylvia, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Shumway, Elizabeth, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Nicholas, Edith N., undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Rejections, 02/1948 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Perpetual, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Mrs. J. S. Winns Scholarship Committee, 07/1948-07/1950 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Columbian Women, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - National Bank of Washington: Bank Statements, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Statements and paid bills, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Columbian Women: Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Columbian Women: Scholarships: Marie-Louise Ralph Turner Fund, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Columbian Women, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous Permanent files, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Officers and Chairpeople, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Benefits, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Education Association, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Members, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Honorary members, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Life Members, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Minutes, 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Miscellaneous Minutes, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Constitution, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Treasurer's reports, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Contributions and gifts, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Columbian Women, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dues, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Deposits, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Disbursments Journal, 12/1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - CW Business, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Income account, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Reciept journal, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Reciepts journal, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Deposit tickets, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Deposit tickets, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Savings Account Perpetual, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Treasurer's reports, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - CW Bicentennial Material, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Perpetual bank, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Paid Bills FY 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Stationery, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Assorted Stuff, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Treasurer's records, correspondence, Scholarship Committee, 1969-1997; Series 5; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains records of the Treasurer, the Scholarship Committee, and correspondence. They date from 1969 to 1997.
  - Small box containing Membership entries, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Estate of Mary Carson, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Crestar Bank Statements - Operating Account, 1990-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Crestar Bank Statements - Savings Account, 1990-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Statements, 1988-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Audit Reports, 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1969-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gifts, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Directory Changes, 1988-1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Investments, 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Columbia First CD, 1987-1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Redeemed CDs, 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - National Bank of Washington Checking Account, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - National Bank of Washington Savings Account, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - General Ledger Sheets, 1987-1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Directories, events, and history, 1897-2005; Series 6; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains directories, press releases, flyers, correspondence, invitations, programs, newspaper clippings, meeting minutes, reports, by-laws, memorandums, biographical information, and written histories. They range in date from 1897 to 2005. The materials concern membership directories, scholarships, events, "Security's Envoy", exhibits, history, and individual members.
  - Clubs, Societies, Organizations--Columbian Women, 1918 ca.-06/10/2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clubs, Societies, Organizations--Columbian Women--Fund-Raising, 11/26/1940-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clubs, Societies, Organizations--Columbian Women--History, 1931-10/06/1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Clubs, Societies, Organizations--Columbian Women--Members--Individuals (alpha), 02/17/1897-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clubs, Societies, Organizations--Columbian Women--Membership Directories, 1934-73, 1983 [1/2], 1934-1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Clubs, Societies, Organizations--Columbian Women--Membership Directories, 1934-73, 1983 [2/2], 1969-2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clubs, Societies, Organizations--Columbian Women--Scholarships, 03/02/1941-12/17/1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Clubs, Societies, Organizations--Columbian Women--Special Events, 04/27/1934-06/11/2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Videotapes, 1977-1978; Series 7; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 2)
  This series contains seven U-matic tapes from the Columbian Women. They range in date from 1977-1978.
  - Columbian Women: U matic tape, "Bridging the Gap", 1977 ca. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    U-matic tape from the Columbian Women. The label reads, "George Washington University/ Continuing Education for Women Center/ 'Bridging the Gap' / 23 min. " It was donated to the University Archives from the Columbian Women in June 2005.
  - Columbian Women: U matic tape, "Community Outreach", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    U-matic tape from the Columbian Women. The label reads, " 'Community Outreach' Anne Ralph (CEW)/ VT 77-2 / Time 15:25 / sd track 1/ col " It was donated to the University Archives from the Columbian Women in June 2005.
  - Columbian Women: U matic tape, "Counseling Women", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    U-matic tape from the Columbian Women. The label reads, " 'Counseling Women' Anne Ralph (CEW)/ VT 77-5/ Time 16:13 / sd track 1/ col " It was donated to the University Archives from the Columbian Women in June 2005.
  - Columbian Women: U matic tape, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    U-matic tape from the Columbian Women. The label reads, " 'Counseling Women' / VT 77-5/ Time 16:13; 'Program Development'/ VT 77-10/ Time 17:35; 'Testing and Evaluation' VT 77-78/ Time 18:00; 'Community Outreach'/ VT77-2/ Time 15:25; 'Which Way Cew' / VT 77-17:40/ Time 17:40/ Anne Ralph (CEW) Audio Track 1/ Col ". It was donated to the University Archives from the Columbian Women in June 2005.
  - Columbian Women: U matic tape, 08/24/1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    U-matic tape from the Columbian Women. The label reads, " Dr. Ruth Osborn/ Houstan, August 24, 1978/ 'The Morning Show' KHOU-TV/ and 'Calender'". It was donated to the University Archives from the Columbian Women in June 2005.
  - Columbian Women: U matic tape "Moving into Management", 04/24/1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    U-matic tape from the Columbian Women. The label reads, " U.S. General Accounting Office/ 'Moving into Management' / Federal Womens Day/ April 24, 1978". It was donated to the University Archives from the Columbian Women in June 2005.
  - Columbian Women: U matic tape "Morning Break", 10/03/1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    U-matic tape from the Columbian Women. The label reads, " 'Morning Break' / Oct. 3, 1978 / with Marvella Bayh". It was donated to the University Archives from the Columbian Women in June 2005.
- Ramona Stoltz papers, 1966-2009; 1999-2008; Series 8; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence, flyers, a directory, meeting minutes, financial records, and articles. The records date from 1966-2009. These records were compiled by Ramona Stoltz. Ms. Stolz graduated from GW with a B.A. in International Affairs. Ms. Stoltz has been a member of Columbian Women for more than ten years and has served in many leadership positions including president, first vice president, and as a member of the planning team for the 2003 Women's Leadership Conference.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Gift of Ramona Stoltz, 12/02/2009 (2009.069)
  - Alumni Service Award, 2001-2002; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Columbian Woman Audit Committee, 2002-2008; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2009; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - GW in the news, 1966-2001; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Directory of the Columbian Women of the George Washington University, 1999-2003; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Financial records, 2003-2006; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Flyers, 2009; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes Edna Landsiedel recording secretary [1/2], 1969-1982; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes Edna Landsiedel recording secretary [2/2], 1983-1988; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Postlude for Jane Lingo, 2007; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Women's Leadership Conference, 2003-2004; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 11)